Nearly 70% of projects fail due to poor
planning and lack of coordination. But
the right tools can make all the
difference. That's why Funboards is
rapidly gaining popularity among project
managers, agencies, remote teams, and
solo premers. With free and premium
versions available for WordPress users,
you can choose the perfect one for you.
But which one truly fits your projects
requirements? Let's find out. Whether
you are a free user or a pro, you can
easily create unlimited project boards
to manage multiple projects
effortlessly. You can also add as many
stages as you need to fit your project
plan. And the unlimited task creation
option that comes with both versions
ensures your projects are divided into
doable tasks. If you wish to highlight
any task among many, some pre-built
covers are available in the free
version. but the pro level up the game
with the custom cover upload capability.
While custom field creation is all set
to cater to your specific requirements
in crucial times, the template creation
that comes with the pro can save you
from repeatedly creating the same kind
of tasks. Then I have another pro
feature to boost your productivity, the
recurring task. It helps you handle
repetitive task effectively by setting
their frequency to meet your needs.
Also, default assignees can be set for
specific stages, ensuring the right
people are assigned automatically
without extra
effort. Upgrading to the pro also
unlocks attachments, which allows you to
share files or resources with team
members for better collaboration and
onpoint task completion. Another
standout feature where the Pro truly
shines is subtask creation. It breaks
down a big task into small chunks with
ease. Besides, you can easily turn it
into a task or convert any task into a
subtask considering its
importance. Before we move on, let's
talk about another pro feature, time
tracking. You can estimate a fixed
amount of time to complete any task.
Creating an arge for your team to speed
up your project completion. Once your
task are organized, having a quick and
clear overview is essential. That's why
Flen Boards kept the list and can one
view open for everyone. But to see every
detail as a calendar, the Pro is the way
to go. Not only that, the free version
gives you the control to choose any
gradient or solid color to personalize
the background of your project board.
Whereas the Pro sweetens the deal with
custom image upload
options. Hold on, things are about to
get better with easy on boarding of team
members. You can easily add team members
from your WordPress site using the free
version. If you want to add members who
are not part of your WordPress
ecosystem, you must invite them. For
that, you must have the pro version
installed. Once the team members are
onboarded, the comment section is all
yours for coordination among your team
members. No matter if you are a free or
pro user. In case you are managing a
project of multiple teams and want to
assign rules to your team members, the
members role can be handy and the pro
gives you the full control of it.
Speaking of the perks of having the pro
version, how can I forget about the
front end portal? It's a fantastic way
of collaborating with clients and team
members while keeping the backend
operations hidden. The Flynn roadmap
add-on which comes with Flynn Boards Pro
unites everyone involved in a project
from planning to execution and says
towards success in the most strategic
way. Another special edge you get with
Pro is the report. It shows you
everything you need to know about your
project. Finally, I have the
integrations. Its easy connections with
Flint CRM, Flint forms and Flint
supports extend its functionality by
many miles. Want to craft automation,
create task via form submission or
support ticket submission to keep things
organized? You are in control. And
that's the breakdown. While Sendboards
Free covers the basic of managing any
project, Pro takes it to the next level
with advanced control, powerful
features, and effortless collaboration.
Take your time, compare the features,
and decide. Will Fin Boots fee free be
enough or are the premium pro features
exactly what you need? The final call is
yours. Make up your mind and take
control of your project success with
Finn Boots today.
[Music]